carminashoemaker.us 2016-05-02

# Privacy Policy - Carmina Shoemaker US

**What information do we  collect and when do we collect it? **

At Carmina Shoemaker the type of information that we collect may be personal information such as your name, address, e-mail, etc. We collect this information when we ask you to provide your details in order that you may take part in our promotions or when you first place an order and register as a client. We will ask you to give your authorization actively  in order to e-mail our Newsletter, offers or seasonal catalogue to you. In addition, when you visit our website, we collect clickstream tracking data (server address, domain name, etc.) This information helps us to statistically improve our service. 

**How do we use it?**

The information supplied helps us to draw up statistics or improve our website functionalities and to provide the services we offer you at the same. We also use the information to send you information by e-mail, offers and news in relation to our products only. You will receive this information if you have authorized us to send it to you ticking the relevant box. 

**Who manages it?**

Personal data shall be managed in accordance with the data protection laws in force for the time being and this privacy policy. 

**How do we protect it?  **

All information supplied is stored in secure networks and may only be accessed by authorized staff, limited to those who are required to keep the information confidential. Whenever personal information is provided on the Internet there is however the risk that third parties unrelated to us may intercept that information. We cannot therefore take responsibility for any use made of the information you provide us with at your risk. 

**Who has access to your  information and to what extent?**

We will only disclose your data when required by law to do so. We shall not sell, deal in or transfer to third parties any information whatsoever which you may provide without your prior consent and in accordance with the data protection laws in force for the time being.  

**Links  **

In order to improve our website, we may introduce links to third parties to whom this privacy policy may not be applicable and who are beyond our control. Your access to those sites is therefore your responsibility and you should check their privacy policy. No URL link may be made to Carmina Shoemaker’s website without Carmina Shoemaker’s prior consent.

**Use of cookies  **

A cookie is a small quantity of data transferred by the website you are visiting to your computer for identification purposes to collect information on your visits and be thereby able to improve your website browsing. Cookies may be used to check your activity at our website and get to know details, for instance, about the products you buy. You may switch off all cookies if you do not wish to receive them and/or have your computer warn you whenever they are being used. You must in both cases change your browser settings. Bear in mind that if you set the computer to reject cookies, you may be limiting the functionality of the website you visit and might not be able to access some of its capabilities. 

**Children’s Privacy**

Carmina Shoemaker would ask minors’ parents and guardians to be aware that their children could conceivably visit our website, and it is therefore advisable that they warn them not to provide any personal information on any website without your prior consent. Carmina Shoemaker is always concerned about children’s safety. 

**Accessing, correcting and eliminating your  data. **

You may access, eliminate or correct your personal data at any time and the use we make of that data. If you wish to exercise any of these rights, send us an e-mail to info@carminashoemaker.com or a letter by ordinary post to CARMINA SHOEMAKER Crta.Palma-Alcudia, Km.30,300 , 07300 (Inca-Mallorca).

**Changes to the Privacy Policy.  **

Carmina Shoemaker reserves the right to change this privacy policy either as required by changes in the laws or to cover new developments at our website. We would therefore ask you to regularly check our privacy policy. 

**Contacting us.**

If you wish to let us have your comments regarding our website or our privacy policy you may send an e-mail to info@carminashoemaker.com .

**Consent  **

By using this website you consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy and to our terms and conditions. Otherwise, please do not provide us with personal data and leave this website.

**Online Policy**

This privacy policy does not extend to the operation of the entire Internet which is beyond our control. This online privacy policy applies only to the information collected through our website.
